{
  "flashCards": [
    {
      "title": "Stack Operations",
      "description": "Data Structure Questions and Answers – Stack Operations – 1",
      "flashCards": [
        {
          "questionType": "scq",
          "question": "Process of inserting an element in stack is called ____________",
          "options": [
            "Create",
            "Push",
            "Evaluation",
            "Pop"
          ],
          "answer": "Push"
        },
        {
          "questionType": "mcq",
          "question": "Which of the following is not the application of stack?",
          "options": [
            "A parentheses balancing program",
            "Tracking of local variables at run time",
            "Compiler Syntax Analyzer",
            "Data Transfer between two asynchronous process"
          ],
          "answers": [
            "A parentheses balancing program",
            "Tracking of local variables at run time",
            "Compiler Syntax Analyzer"
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionType": "mwq",
          "question": "Stack follows which principle?",
          "options": [],
          "answer": "Last In First Out"
        },
        {
          "questionType": "swq",
          "question": "Removing element from stack is called:",
          "answer": "pop"
        }
      ],
      "mode": "public",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "title": "Stack Operations",
      "description": "Data Structure Questions and Answers – Stack Operations – 1",
      "flashCards": [
        {
          "questionType": "scq",
          "question": "Process of inserting an element in stack is called ____________",
          "options": [
            "Create",
            "Push",
            "Evaluation",
            "Pop"
          ],
          "answer": "Push"
        },
        {
          "questionType": "mcq",
          "question": "Which of the following is not the application of stack?",
          "options": [
            "A parentheses balancing program",
            "Tracking of local variables at run time",
            "Compiler Syntax Analyzer",
            "Data Transfer between two asynchronous process"
          ],
          "answers": [
            "A parentheses balancing program",
            "Tracking of local variables at run time",
            "Compiler Syntax Analyzer"
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionType": "mwq",
          "question": "Stack follows which principle?",
          "options": [],
          "answer": "Last In First Out"
        },
        {
          "questionType": "swq",
          "question": "Removing element from stack is called:",
          "answer": "pop"
        }
      ],
      "mode": "private",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "title": "Queue in Java",
      "description": "Java Questions & Answers – Data Structures-Queue",
      "flashCards": [
        {
          "questionType": "scq",
          "question": "What is the correct method used to insert and delete items from the queue?",
          "options": [
            " push and pop",
            "enqueue and dequeue",
            "enqueue and peek",
            "add and remove"
          ],
          "answer": "enqueue and dequeue"
        },
        {
          "questionType": "swq",
          "question": "Which data structure is used in Breadth First Traversal of a graph?",
          "answer": "Queue"
        }
      ],
      "mode": "public",
      "id": 3
    }
  ]
}